{
  "calc:1": {
    "question": "∫ x + 1 dx ",
    "answer": "1 + c",
    "options": [
      "1 + c",
      "2 + c",
      "c",
      "x + c"
    ]
  },
  "calc:2": {
    "question": "∫ 2x + 1 dx ",
    "answer": "2 + c",
    "options": [
      "2 + c",
      "2x + c",
      "c",
      "3 + c"
    ]
  },
  "calc:3": {
    "question": "∫ x² dx ",
    "answer": "2x + c",
    "options": [
      "2x + c",
      "x + 1",
      "x + 2c",
      "2x + 1 + c"
    ]
  },
  "calc:4": {
    "question": "∫ x³ dx ",
    "answer": "3x² + c",
    "options": [
      "3x² + c",
      "x² + c",
      "3x²",
      "x² + c"
    ]
  },
  "calc:5": {
    "question": "∫ x³ + 3 dx ",
    "answer": "3x² + c",
    "options": [
      "3x² + c",
      "x + c",
      "3x²",
      "x + c"
    ]
  },
  "calc:6": {
    "question": "∫ 2x³ - 2 dx ",
    "answer": "6x² + c",
    "options": [
      "6x² + c",
      "x² + c",
      "3x²",
      "x² + c"
    ]
  },
  "calc:7": {
    "question": "∫ 5x² dx ",
    "answer": "10x + c",
    "options": [
      "10x + c",
      "5x² + c",
      "5x²",
      "x² + c"
    ]
  },
  "calc:8": {
    "question": "∫ 7x² dx ",
    "answer": "14x + c",
    "options": [
      "14x + c",
      "7x² + c",
      "7x²",
      "x² + c"
    ]
  },
  "calc:9": {
    "question": "∫ 5x³ - 2x² dx ",
    "answer": "15x² - 4x + c",
    "options": [
      "15x² - 4x + c",
      "5x³ - 2x² + c",
      "5x³ - 2x²",
      "x² + c"
    ]
  },
  "calc:10": {
    "question": "∫ 2x³ - 4x² dx ",
    "answer": "6x² - 8x + c",
    "options": [
      "6x² - 8x + c",
      "2x³ - 4x² + c",
      "2x³ - 4x²",
      "x² + c"
    ]
  }
}